So nice to meet you, Miguel. I'm Lura, your personal AI English tutor. Talk with me for
just five minutes a day and see how you become a confident English speaker. So tell me, where
are you from? Hello, Lura. Nice to meet you. My name is Miguel. I'm from Columbia, Latin America.
It's a pleasure to meet you. Thank you. It's great to meet you. Columbia has such a rich
culture and beautiful landscapes. What do you love most about living there? Well, I was born
here. I don't know about other countries, but I like everything here, I believe. That's wonderful.
It's great that you appreciate everything about your home. If you could visit any country someday,
where would you like to go? Well, definitely the US, the United States, because when I was a child,
I saw a lot of movies about, you know, Disney World, things like that. And I have a good image
of it. And one day I want to travel there. That sounds like an amazing dream. Just a small
correction. Instead of saying I see a lot of movies, you could say I saw a lot of movies
since you're talking about your childhood. Saw is the past tense, which fits better in this
context. What movies from Disney have you enjoyed the most?
Well, actually, I don't remember that one because, you know, when I was a child. But
Walt Disney makes movies for kids, you know. No worries at all. Disney movies can be really
memorable, even if we forget specific titles. Do you remember any characters or themes that
stood out to you from those movies? Well, I don't remember anything in particular about Disney,
but I remember other movies that I really like nowadays, such as The Matrix, for example. It's
a good movie. It's a science fiction action film. The Matrix is a fantastic choice. It really blends
action and thought provoking themes, doesn't it? What do you like most about that movie?
Well, it's so interesting because it's like a reality, albeit an exaggerated one. Perhaps
something like that could happen in the future. I don't know.
That's a fascinating perspective. The idea of blending reality with technology makes it so
thought provoking. Do you enjoy other science fiction movies or is The Matrix your favorite?
Recently, I have seen several movies, including romance films. I enjoy them quite a bit as well.
For example, I recently watched a movie called Before Sunrise. It's a beautiful film. I don't
know if you're familiar with it, but Before Sunrise is a romance movie.
That's a fascinating perspective. The idea of blending reality with technology makes it
so thought provoking. Do you enjoy other science fiction movies or is The Matrix your favorite?
Recently, I have seen several movies, including romance films. I enjoy them quite a bit as well.
For example, I recently watched a movie called Before Sunrise. It's a beautiful film. I don't
know if you're familiar with it, but Before Sunrise is a romance movie.
Before Sunrise is a beautiful film. The way it captures a deep connection
between two people over just one night is really special.
Another movie that I saw today is The Notebook. It's another romance film that is just as beautiful.
The Notebook is such a heartfelt story. The emotions and the connection between the characters
really resonate with many people. Do you have a favorite scene from either of those romance movies?
Well, another movie is Before Sunrise. In that film, I remember a scene that I really like.
It's when the boy tries to approach the girl and he attempts to get on the ride.
It's not really a roller coaster ride. It's more like a roller coaster ride.
The movie is about the same as the movie. It's not really a roller coaster ride. It's not like a roller
coaster ride. I remember thinking about it the whole time. I just like the way it was shot.
the ride. It's not really a roller coaster, it's part of the attractions, but I can't remember the
name of that ride. It was a little dangerous because he was trying to express that he wanted
to go out with her, but he jokingly pretended to commit suicide. I don't know if you're familiar
with that scene from before sunrise.
It sounds like you're talking about a memorable scene that really captures the intensity of young
love. The mix of humor and seriousness in that moment is what makes it so impactful.
Yes, exactly. That scene was so impactful because it was both dangerous and funny. The girl was so
intimidated by the guy, but he finally figured it out. He then went to the park and started
to take her out on a date. In the end, he achieved his goal with her, which was funny, but also a
little crazy.
That scene really highlights the mix of emotions that come with falling in love. It's interesting how humor can lighten even the most intense moments.
Yeah, you're right. I agree with you.
I'm glad we agree. It's fascinating how love stories can intertwine humor and drama. Do you enjoy watching romance movies with friends or do you prefer to watch them alone?
It's equally important for me to be alone or to have company. I feel good whether I'm by myself or with others.
It's wonderful that you feel comfortable both alone and with company. It shows a great balance. It was great getting to know you today, and I look forward to our next lesson tomorrow.
See you tomorrow at 010, where I'll share your first daily word.